ALCHEMY OF SOULS
PART 2
We are married.
Please give us your blessings.
Nonsense. I did not allow this marriage.
Jang Uk, I will never allow you
to take my daughter.
I am not asking for your permission.
Like I said,
we are already married.
Bu-yeon.
Answer me.
This cannot be, right?
My kindhearted daughter
could not have possibly deceived me
and married that man.
Am I right?
I will never abandon you, Mother.
Yes. Right.
You are so precious to me.
However,
I cannot live the life you want for me.
That is why I married him.
And from now on,
we will be together.
I do not believe you.
He is holding my daughter hostage
and forcing her to lie.
This wedding is a lie.
Are you all going to sit back
and watch this nonsense?
Jang Uk.
You vowed never to abuse your power
on the life of Park Jin,
the former leader of Songrim.
How dare you wed the heiress of Jinyowon
without Jinyowon's consent?
Leave her here and go.
If not,
Park Jin will pay
for all the deeds you have committed.
I did not use any of my powers.
Are you so terrified
that you would use him to threaten me?
Terrified?
You must have nothing to fear
due to those powers of yours.
But this is the Unanimous Assembly.
We are not fearful of you.
In that case,
watch closely
as I take her away from here.
I thought being
the acting leader was enough.
So why must I come here
on my uncle's behalf as well?
We must hurry.
The Unanimous Assembly must have begun.
Right.
I heard you were the acting leader.
So you are attending
the Unanimous Assembly as well.
I did not know you would be here.
I heard that your sister was found
and she will be introduced as the heir.
I heard you posted her portrait
throughout Daeho Fortress.
It was nothing.
Your sister was missing.
That was the least I could do.
Why did you do that
when no one asked you to?
Now that her face has been revealed,
she will be locked up forever.
Poor thing.
Locked up?
Something must have happened
at the Unanimous Assembly.
He has incredible skills.
Did you see that?
He unleashed such power
when he did not even unsheathe his sword.
The ice stone has the energy of the sky.
If Jang Uk wants to,
he could take all of our souls
using his powers!
Still, we have here with us
some of Daeho's most powerful mages.
We will be a laughingstock
if we let him go!
Please calm down.
One party does not believe
that they are married,
and the other party claims that they are.
I have an idea.
Bring forth a witness
who can verify your marriage.
Why is a witness necessary?
Because no one believes you.
Bring forth a witness,
and we will let you go with our blessings.
But if you do not,
you are not justified
to take Jinyowon's heiress with you,
and you must leave alone.
I see that you are still
hung up on justifications.
If my powers can be
considered justification,
I would like
to see you try arguing with that.
Gosh.
I guess you cannot prove it.
I can.
And we have
a witness.
Right here.
She is with child?
Do you not consider
this baby to be the best witness
to our wedding?
How can we believe you?
Right.
We have a physician here.
Master Heo, please take a look.
I can only tell
if at least 21 days have passed.
Uk.
When did you two become intimate?
Why would you ask such a thing?
How embarrassing.
We need to be sure.
Lady Jin.
Seeing how they are close,
should you not give them your permission?
Marriage is a family affair.
The Unanimous Assembly does not
need to talk further about this.
Let us put an end to this.
End it.
Hey, Uk.
You were here too?
Bu-yeon.
Why are you leaving?
I am married to him.
So I will be moving in
with my husband.
Your husband?
I told you before that I was waiting
for my groom to take me away.
He came, and I am leaving with him.
So he was the one
who got her out of that room.
Did your sister just say
that she got married to Uk?
I see.
If Jang Uk has become
Lady Jin's son-in-law,
I do not see the need
to move Jinyowon to another family.
I agree.
It is Jang Uk, after all.
No one would dare to attack Jinyowon.
Ho-gyeong.
You have put on quite a show
introducing Bu-yeon to everyone.
In any case,
Jinyowon will remain safe and strong
thanks to your great son-in-law.
Young Master, welcome home.
Hey.
You are back again, my lady.
Yes, I am.
Young Master.
Where did you go without telling me?
- And why are you--
- Maidservant Kim.
She must be exhausted today as well,
so please prepare her a room.
Today, you have dressed appropriately
as a member of the Jin family.
I attended the Unanimous Assembly.
The Unanimous Assembly?
Is that where our young master
picked you up?
Yes.
But this time,
I will be settling here for good.
I hope we get along, Maidservant Kim.
Right.
So the person
Bu-yeon gave her heart to was Uk.
Does this mean
the two were dating?
When did they first meet?
It must have been that day
when Uk entered Jinyowon.
Was that already 21 days ago?
- Twenty-one days?
- It is a long story.
Could that be true too?
- But Dang-gu,
- What?
do you really believe it?
That Uk finally let go of Mu-deok…
and fell in love with someone else?
Of course not.
That is absurd.
I am sure there is a reason for all this.
But what could it be?
You are a relic of Jinyowon, right?
Thanks to you, I was able to get married.
Wait…
Did I really turn you off?
Or…
did Uk turn you off
so he could take me away?
Of course not.
If I could turn it off,
then could I turn it back on again?
This is his sword.
How pretty.
What is going on?
That lantern.
Did you turn it on?
Was it you?
I was the only one here…
so probably.
Why are you not sure?
Something just flashed before my eyes.
I think it was a memory.
It must be true that regaining my memories
will bring back my powers.
Do it again.
See? I did that.
Well done.
I could not recover my memories until now
since I was locked up.
Look.
Now that there are external stimuli,
it is all coming back to me.
This way, you can continue
regaining your memories and divine powers.
I am glad I brought you here.
Thank goodness.
I was worried because you seemed mad.
That was because
you made up a fake witness.
Was it not because of my mother?
Was it because of the baby?
We got out of there safely
thanks to our baby.
I already expected your mother
to react that way.
As for the baby--
You are making it seem like
you are actually pregnant.
What do we do now?
That physician, Heo Yeom,
wants to check up on me
after the twenty-first day.
I cannot tell him the truth.
Then what?
Do you want us to make a baby by then?
Why? What is it?
I was hoping
for this.
I hoped you were the one
who turned off the lantern
and I hoped that you would come for me…
despite being of no use to you.
Even if I did turn it off,
it would not be
due to the reasons you were hoping for.
You know that.
So what are you going to do?
If you want, I can help you create
that witness you must bring
to Sejukwon by the twenty-first day.
That is, if you give up
on that futile hope of yours.
Let us say this was
how we created our witness.
We are married, after all.
I cannot say I did it alone.
You said you would help.
Do not resent me for this.
Will you keep lying about a witness?
What is it now?
Stop being unpredictable.
- What is it?
- Do not mind me.
- What is this?
- My mother sewed the tracking thread
into my flesh.
It is tightening and causing me pain.
She must be…
calling for me.
I cannot let you stay with him.
Come back,
my dear daughter, Bu-yeon.
Regardless of the circumstances,
how could a mother sew
such a thing onto her daughter?
I cannot believe this.
Goodness, you must be feeling
excruciating pain.
How about you return to Jinyowon for now?
I will tell our young master
to escort you.
Do not do that.
I said I would endure the pain.
Please do not send me away.
How could you possibly endure such pain?
It is brazen to desire something
without being willing
to endure the pain.
A pain that does not kill me
will eventually…
set me free.
Young Master.
Young Lady Bu-yeon is in a lot of pain.
So?
Does she want to return?
No, she vehemently refuses.
I applied some ointment for the pain,
but it is not helping.
She said she would endure it.
Just give her more ointment.
I thought she was his wife.
Why is he being so cold to her?
Mother.
Please stop.
It is too painful.
Her face was
shockingly identical to Naksu's,
but her build and aura
were completely different.
Naksu was neither that dainty nor small.
I need to find out more about Jin Bu-yeon.
- So-i should be coming for her medicine.
- Yes, my lord.
I will use her.
- Here we go.
- Let me see.
- One more.
- Really?
- I got it!
- Darn it.
- Here you go.
- Where is it?
Wait here. Goodness.
Ninety-three.
Ninety-four.
Ninety-five.
Ninety-six.
Ninety-seven.
Ninety-eight.
Ninety-nine.
One hundred.
Sang-gu, are you all right?
What do I do?
Do you want to save your brother?
Then pay me back.
You sold your farmland.
Give me the money you got.
I do not have any. I already used it all.
Is that so?
I will count to 200 this time.
Try hard to remember where the money is.
Dunk him.
Sang-gu!
Two.
- Three.
- Sang-gu!
- Madam.
- Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Bu-yeon.
Why are you making me hurt you?
Come back.
What have you done?
My wife cannot sleep.
Please refrain from calling her
in the middle of the night.
As you already know,
we are newlyweds.
There is no pain anymore.
Mother must have stopped.
In return for the medicine,
he wants you to bring her to him.
Jin Bu-yeon?
Lady Jin's daughter?
Is it really her?
That is not important.
Just follow the Gwanju's orders.
You are alive to this day
despite the blood parasite in you
only because of his medicine.
And I am showing my gratitude
by doing everything he wants.
I will take her to that room
in Cheonbugwan.
Have you told the person
who has been giving me this medicine
that I wanted to see them?
They said there was no need for that
and refused.
But I do know who they are
and what they do.
Is her name So-i?
So you two have met.
She is the owner
of a notorious gambling den.
Rumor has it she does illegal business,
and Cheonbugwan has her back.
I felt extremely uneasy
knowing that I was giving you medicine
from a woman like her.
Where is this gambling den?
It is in Gaema Village.
Are you taking that medicine
because you are ill?
Are you staying here instead of at Songrim
to hide your illness?
That is not true.
I feel more comfortable here.
You do not need to worry about me.
Young Master.
Did you go somewhere?
Why are you still up, Maidservant Kim?
How can I sleep in this situation?
Would you rather watch me lose sleep
and explain everything tomorrow?
Well…
Maidservant Kim.
I am sorry for getting married abruptly.
I should have asked for your permission.
In that case,
you should have a proper wedding ceremony.
Before then, I will not consider her
to be the lady of the house.
I will continue calling you "young master"
instead of "my lord."
All right, then. Prepare for a wedding.
Do you mean that?
Not mine, but yours.
- Young Master.
- I am already married.
So you can get married to him as well.
You can do that.
What will you do
after I get married?
She and I will get what we desire.
She was locked up
and hidden from everyone.
Now, she will be free.
As will I.
Can I interpret that
as you trying your best
to let go of the past?
In that case,
I will say what I have kept to myself
for the past three years.
Please get rid of
the red bird egg that you keep
where you have been stabbed.
Why do you keep the yin-and-yang jade
you shared with the dead?
That jade
brings two people to each other.
I am terrified
that the dead girl will come
to take you away.
Do not worry.
She has never
called me with this.
She is dead.
The egg that you nurtured
with great care hatched
into an atrocious bird of prey.
And it gravely wounded you before it died.
So please
destroy it.
The reason why I still have this is
so that I will know
that she really is dead.
I can only believe
that she will never come back
if I can see it with my own eyes.
Because…
I did not witness her death.
Who are they talking about?
A bird egg?
I can finally sleep in peace
since the pain is gone.
Should I tell him
that I am no longer in pain?
He could be worried about me.
He does not worry about me.
Young Lady Bu-yeon.
They are like family to Young Master Jang.
I am Jin Bu-yeon,
the eldest daughter of the Jin family.
It is nice to meet you.
Is it really true
that you and Uk are married?
That is why she is here.
Since you are married,
let me congratulate you.
They are not married yet.
We will have a formal wedding ceremony.
Until then, she is still
the eldest daughter of Jinyowon
and Young Master Jang's betrothed.
Seeing how you are still his betrothed,
you must not be with child after all.
I am sorry.
I lied to prevent a fight from occurring.
You are very daring.
Have I ever treated you before?
You seem familiar.
I doubt it.
I was treated
by the best physician in Daeho Fortress.
I am the best physician here.
Who else could it be? Tell me their name.
Master Heo, please stop.
She never left Jinyowon.
From what I heard,
she suffers from memory loss.
Memory loss?
I was seriously ill,
and I have no recollection of the past.
However,
I still have the ability to see energy
as I did as a child.
I see some impressive energy
within you two.
You are of the few mages
with exceptionally strong powers.
Anyone could sense that.
As for you,
your energy may not be impressive.
But it is pure and bright.
Anyone can see
that Dang-gu has a good personality.
That cannot be considered a special power.
You have a similar energy
to my sister, Cho-yeon.
They are both pure and light.
I believe Cho-yeon has told you
about me, right?
Are you seeing Cho-yeon again?
- No.
- We just met to discuss Bu-yeon.
- Dang-gu.
- Did you meet her?
- Pardon?
Yes.
And I have been sensing
two people's energy back there.
Do not be absurd.
Come out if you are back there!
Young Lady Heo.
What are you doing there?
Then what did you see in Uk?
He had the energy of the sky.
That is right.
Uk had died and was only revived
thanks to that energy.
I heard.
Since I can see his energy,
I promise to stay by his side
and protect him.
What do you think about her?
I do believe that she is a priestess
with unique powers.
I believe she got married
to our young master
to avoid becoming an heiress.
And our young master
wants to get married for my sake.
For your sake?
He said I do not need
to worry about him anymore.
He is encouraging me to get married.
You understood that, right?
I am always prepared
to welcome you with open arms.
But your heart still seems to be troubled.
You do not need to rush.
I will not pull you toward me
if you are not ready.
But your heart is racing, my lord.
Despite what I just said,
How can I possibly hide
even my longing for you?
I…
have desires too.
Master Heo does not seem
to like Young Lady Bu-yeon very much.
He was disapproving
and said she looked familiar.
To be honest,
she seemed familiar to me as well.
I believe I have seen her before.
How fascinating.
You recognized it at first glance.
Right? I have seen her before.
That is right.
That dress belonged to Madam Do-hwa.
She often wore it before she got married.
That is right.
No wonder she seemed familiar.
After seeing Do-hwa in that dress,
I wrote a poem for her.
They do say
that first love is unforgettable.
Even a slow-witted person like you
recognized her dress at first glance.
- Your heart must have fluttered.
- That is not true.
This heart is racing right now
because of you.
Forget it.
Listen carefully.
Can you not hear my heart?
I know.
I was just joking.
You can let me go.
I am finally embracing you,
so how could
I possibly let go that easily?
You do not need to walk me home.
I may have lost my memory,
but I am not stupid.
Please do not misunderstand.
She only said it out of concern for you.
She has a hard time believing
that you are married to Uk.
To be honest,
I find it hard to believe as well.
She asked me to check on you.
She could not defend me
out of fear of our mother.
But she is pure and kindhearted.
Has your wound
from the tracking thread healed?
She is glad that it will not hurt anymore.
Did Cho-yeon hide the thread somewhere?
Without my mother's knowing?
So that is why it stopped hurting.
Pardon?
You must not know
about last night's incident.
What do you mean?
The thread is gone.
Uk broke into Jinyowon last night
and destroyed it.
Jinyowon was in chaos
because of him.
Were you really not aware of it?
I was not.
He just told me…
to endure the pain.
Uk spends most of the day
in the Dark Forest,
which gets its name
from the dense cypress trees.
You will see stone towers
deep in the forest.
Every time he kills a soul shifter,
he builds one.
It is like a graveyard.
People are too scared
to even go near them.
He seems to prefer that
as he is often there.
I was told he would be here.
But he is not.
Are these the soul shifters' graves?
One of the graves
belongs to Naksu.
She will end up finding it.
You must have killed
the infamous soul shifter as well.
She died.
That soul shifter's grave
must be here as well.
- They are bird's eggs.
- We can have one each.
I pick red. You can have the blue one.
I did not even touch the tower.
But why did it collapse?
This is not just any stone.
I saw this stone in my memory back there.
Did I see it in Jinyowon?
Did I see it as a child?
Who could she be?
Jin Bu-yeon is Mu-deok,
and Mu-deok is already dead.
If this came from Jinyowon,
should I ask Cho-yeon about it?
Hey! Stop right there!
Stop!
- Goodness.
Gosh.
- I am sorry.
- Watch where you are going.
I am sorry.
Lure her toward Cheonbugwan's back door.
Yeom-su will be waiting there.
Yes, my lady.
Once So-i lures Jin Bu-yeon,
I will bring her here.
Once I read her mind
with this soul incense,
I will know for sure
if she really is Jin Bu-yeon.
That is strange.
The stone's energy
is in the other direction.
How did she know to follow me here?
Seeing how you are hiding,
you must know that I was tailing you.
You must be wondering
how I knew to follow you.
I can see energy.
I can see yours even when you are hiding.
And I can see this stone's energy too.
I sense bad energy.
I should not inhale this.
She can see energy?
That is Jin Bu-yeon's divine power.
I should wait until she falls unconscious,
then take her to Cheonbugwan.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
I am here to see the owner.
Go to the last room on that side.
There you are, Madam.
Someone is looking for you.
I smell soporifics.
Jin Bu-yeon?
Why are you here?
I was chasing a pickpocket.
I am here to see someone.
Darn it.
You can hold onto me.
Then you will get wet too.
- That is fine.
- Thank you.
Hold on.
I stayed underwater
after smelling the soporifics.
I almost drowned.
Cover yourself.
But I am not cold.
I must have been mortifying to look at.
Thank you once again.
Should I help you catch the thief?
I retrieved my property.
I do not want to cause a scene,
so I will leave.
Go on and meet whomever you came here for.
It is not urgent, so let me walk with you.
This is a dangerous neighborhood
to walk alone in.
This is Gaema Village.
Many fortune-telling shamans live here.
There are also those who practice sorcery.
That must be
why it feels so dark and cold here.
You should ask Uk to accompany you
to dangerous places like this.
Do you know Jang Uk--
I mean, do you know my husband?
Dang-gu, Uk, and I are childhood friends.
- I see.
- For the past three years,
I was in Seoho Fortress, my hometown,
but I recently returned.
I have already met Dang-gu.
He had bright energy.
As for you…
I envy you for having childhood friends.
By the way,
I think we have been circling
the same path.
I lose my sense of direction
when I am flustered.
I apologize.
I think it is that way.
We already went down that path.
Let us go that way.
I have now become familiar
with these paths.
So follow me.
It is my fault that we went in circles.
I am sorry.
That is fine.
There is nothing wrong
with being airheaded
- as long as you are handsome.
- I was simply flustered.
I am not airheaded.
All right.
I do not think you understand.
I was always the top pupil
during my training in Jeongjingak.
I have mastered all the books,
so people always ask me for help.
That is who I am.
I see.
So you are smart?
That is a pity.
As you can see,
my beauty is unmatched.
But I am not the brightest.
You also seemed like a fool
despite your good looks.
So I felt a sense of kinship.
It is a shame that you are smart.
In that case,
I can deem myself a fool
so we can be two foolish friends.
Thank you.
I am asking because I do not know.
Was there a soul shifter
who could see despite having been blind?
She had blue marks in her eyes,
and Uk saw them from up close.
Do you know who she was?
I believe you are talking about Naksu.
Naksu?
I heard she died.
Correct.
And Uk died by her hands as well.
I see.
She was his enemy.
You must not have known about this.
I did not.
I should be careful not to mention
her name in front of him.
Thank you for letting me know.
She could see energy?
Then she really is Jin Bu-yeon.
Did you not say
that you threw her into a lake
when she was a girl?
Are you worried
that people will find out about that?
It was her dead father who threw her in.
That blind girl did not know
that I was there as well.
Thanks to Jin U-tak
being murdered by Naksu,
everything was swept under the rug.
And that is why you are still alive.
You were a swindler who killed many.
You even put a blood parasite inside you
and pretended to be their fake child.
And yet, I turned you
into an innocent victim
who was controlled by Jin U-tak.
That is right.
I am forever indebted to you.
I know you do not mean that.
But as long as
that parasite lives within you,
you will never be able to leave me.
Because without my medicine,
you will writhe in pain
as your insides melt, and you will die.
Anyway, both of us
and my secret organization
were able to get out alive
thanks to Naksu.
However, I cannot believe
how much she resembles her.
What do you mean?
Bu-yeon is the spitting image of Naksu.
That was why I was wary of her.
Seeing how that girl
does indeed have divine powers,
she must not be a fake daughter
like you were.
So that woman truly is…
Jin Bu-yeon.
I heard there was a drought.
But these flowers are still fresh.
I remembered the flowers you used to love.
I searched throughout Daeho Fortress
to find them.
They are full of energy
since Lake Gyeongcheondaeho's water
flows within them.
My former body
was just like this flower.
The flower is full of moisture.
It is very fresh and beautiful.
The flowers outside
have shriveled up due to lack of energy.
They do not emit a scent either.
Shriveled up due to lack of energy?
They are just like me.
All you have to do is water these flowers
to make them look fresh!
But no matter how much energy I consume,
I am still shriveling up!
You want me to petrify and die
in this body that is not mine.
How dare you mock me?
I am sorry, Your Highness!
Please spare me!
You are
young and fresh.
Would you like to switch bodies with me?
Why would you want
to switch bodies with a mere court lady?
You are our noble Queen.
He is a close cousin of mine
from Seoho Fortress.
He was to marry into the Jin family.
I heard about the Unanimous Assembly.
So Jang Uk became
Jin Ho-gyeong's son-in-law?
Because of that,
it has become more difficult
to take Jinyowon
from the Jin family.
Then what about the rite for the lake?
You said we needed Jinyowon's relic
to get the ice stone from the sky.
How will we open Jinyowon's doors
if that man is there?
We will have to remove
the priestess from his side.
But they are married.
Who will acknowledge that
when they did not even have a wedding?
In addition,
everyone in Daeho knows
that he was betrothed to someone else.
Naksu?
The third anniversary of her death
is around the corner.
I shall summon Naksu's soul once again
to distract Jang Uk.
After that,
Jin Bu-yeon will get married
to her former betrothed.
None of the mages
at the Unanimous Assembly
could stop Jang Uk
from leaving with that priestess.
Is he truly more powerful
than all the mages there?
They let him go
because he said they were married.
Goodness.
They always have their excuses.
I heard that Jin Bu-yeon
has some great divine powers.
Did he marry her
because he needed those powers?
Her portrait was posted throughout Daeho.
Apparently, she is a great beauty.
Because of her looks?
I know Jang Uk pretty well.
He would only seduce a woman to use her,
not because he fell for her looks.
Did they fight?
Something must have happened
between the Queen and her court ladies.
Since His Majesty is avoiding her,
she is venting her anger at the innocent.
To be honest, there is a lot of gossip
about the powder
the Queen has given to the concubines.
Powder…
as in cosmetics? Why?
They think it is cursed
with sorcery that dries out their skin.
Go and retrieve all that powder
and find out where the Queen got it from.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
Look at these pretty shoes.
You are so beautiful.
Please have a look around.
Here. They suit you.
I bet they will look great on you.
You are pretty.
Gosh, then come again next time.
That looks delicious.
I apologize.
Is there something you are looking for?
I heard you sold powder
to the royal palace.
Powder?
I am a eunuch.
She must have sent you.
This way, please.
Goodness. Are you interested in the rouge?
Try it on yourself.
It has a beautiful color.
There is no need.
I am just looking at them.
This is not just any rouge.
This rouge has the power
to sway the men around you.
Is that true?
Do you have a lover
that you want to attract?
I have a husband.
This rouge is quite distinct.
All of our products are one of a kind.
Look.
That eunuch was sent
from the royal palace.
Even the royal palace buys our products.
I guess you did not know.
I sense ominous energy.
The energy here is similar
to that of Gaema Village.
Are you also a shaman from there?
Many shamans buy our products.
I do not need them.
Are you selling this turtle too?
It is not for sale.
It is an ingredient used for our products.
An ingredient?
There are many uses for its shell.
It is quite expensive and rare to find.
You should not touch it.
- Ok-sim!
- Coming.
An ingredient? You poor thing.
Eunuch, do you have some money?
Me?
- Were you referring to me?
- If you do, buy this turtle.
It has good energy.
It will bring you luck.
Do shamans read
turtles' physiognomy as well?
Why would I take it with me?
It will be killed if it stays here.
That would be a pity.
Forget it. You should purchase it, not me.
I have no money right now.
And I am living at someone else's place,
so I cannot be that shameless.
Look.
It is stretching its neck to look at you.
Will you just let it die?
All turtles look like that.
It is not doing that just to look at me.
Raise it yourself.
Since…
you cannot have any children as a eunuch.
It will be worth it.
Children?
Hey, shaman.
You have poor skills,
and that is why you make no money.
Do I look like someone
who would raise a turtle as his own?
I cannot see one's physiognomy,
but I can see their energy.
You may talk coldly,
but your warm heart wants
to save this turtle.
You have rare energy.
It must be because you live at the palace.
That is right. I am…
Go from the royal palace.
Then, Eunuch Go,
please take good care of the turtle.
I pretty much revealed to her
that I was a part of the royal family.
How could she not know that?
Is she a fool?
Your Royal Highness.
I found the powder.
The well suddenly dried up
in a matter of days.
We asked Cheonbugwan to look into it,
but they have not done anything so far.
The drought may have been ongoing,
but a well could not
have dried up so quickly.
Why did you bring him here?
You should have brought
a powerful mage instead.
He said he would look into it
if I paid for his food.
- Who knew he would be incompetent?
- Goodness.
Goodness. The well is filling up again!
What a relief!
Goodness! Thank you!
He is incredible.
I have found five of these
in every well so far.
- Thank you.
Who in the world is doing this?
This is a relief.
Noodles and celebrations go hand in hand.
You fool.
Had you had a proper wedding,
I would have served this dish
to everyone in Songrim.
No. You better not
serve this dish to anyone.
If you serve this on your wedding day
with Maidservant Kim,
I will be angry.
I heard from her.
Did you think marrying her off to me
would help you
die in peace?
Your bride does not
seem to know about this.
Have you not told her yet?
She lacks her divine powers as of now.
She needs to regain her memory to do that.
I already confirmed it.
Then it will not happen anytime soon.
Eat up.
These noodles will be the death of me.
Is that so?
I followed the recipe used in the kitchen.
Apparently, Mu-deok used
to enjoy making those noodles.
I avoided mentioning
her name all this time
because I did not want to hurt you.
However,
I think it failed instead.
You did not visit
the cliff where she met her demise,
did you?
Then why did you raise
that stone tower in the mountain?
Were you not mourning her death?
Were you praying she would come back?
Sang-ho was the one…
who witnessed her getting petrified
and saw her fall
into Lake Gyeongcheondaeho.
Let him recount the incident,
see for yourself,
and then mourn for her.
And if you still want to die after that…
come back here.
I will make you
another dish.
He is not coming home.
Jang Uk.
Goodness.
Young Master Jang is often away
for days on end
without telling us in advance.
Do not wait for him and just go to bed.
He is still not home.
When is he coming?
Gosh.
I wanted to thank him
for destroying the tracking thread.
He will be delighted to hear…
that I regained another memory.
Wait there. I will go to you soon.
Make me another promise
just like you said you would.
I will keep you by my side forever.
If you find yourself
in a life or death situation,
give up on love and choose your life.
That is an order from your master.
Are you done, my lady?
Why is he not coming home?
My lady.
You have been summoned to the study.
Is that so?
How many days has it been?
It is not the young master.
It is not him.
Young Lady Bu-yeon.
Young Master Jang is at Jeongjingak.
I guess you did not know that.
You must be worried.
He has been staying there
ever since you visited Songrim last time.
That must mean you two have not met since.
No one will be able to take care of him
since that place is empty.
So why is he there all by himself?
Maybe someone makes him
uncomfortable at home.
Young Lady Bu-yeon.
Let us bring some clothes for him.
He is there because he feels comfortable.
If you ever get to see him,
please let him know
that I am doing well here.
Please give me anything that he may need,
and I will deliver it to him.
There is no need for me
to give anything to you.
After all, Young Lady Bu-yeon
is betrothed to him.
You do not need to worry
about him from now on.
I understand.
Why is he not coming home?
Could it really be because of me?
Let us go, my dear husband.
I was telling you
to take off that impractical robe.
Why in the world…
If you drink that,
it means we are officially married.
I do not wish to go back.
I like it here. And I like you too.
He is uncomfortable
that I might throw myself at him.
Darn it. He would not
be happy to see me then.
This way, you can continue
regaining your memories and divine powers.
I am glad I brought you here.
He will be delighted if I tell him
that I remembered something.
Maidservant Kim.
I must go see him.
Please pack his things for me.
Young Lady Heo.
Let me come with you.
I miss him too much to just wait.
He seems to be avoiding you.
What if he does not welcome you?
I do not mind that.
I am simply going there
because I miss him.
And Sun-i, it seems like
you want him to feel that way about me.
Why is that?
Is that what your young lady wants?
- She was the first to--
- There seems to be a misunderstanding.
I am worried about you, not jealous.
I know he will not welcome either of us.
You think we are the same.
Are you being humble or condescending?
I am simply giving you advice.
But never mind if you do not get it.
What is that in your hand?
Do you recognize this?
That is
a yin-and-yang jade.
A yin-and-yang jade?
There is a red one and a blue one.
They are drawn to each other's energy.
How is it that you have it?
I picked it up.
I kept it after the stone tower
of the jade's owner fell.
- But I will return it.
- What do you mean?
The owner of that blue jade is dead.
The owner of that jade
is Naksu, the one who stabbed
Young Master Jang in the heart.
Naksu?
I have heard of her before.
She was his enemy.
You really do not know anything.
Put energy into the jade and call for him.
Then you will understand
why no one believed
that you were his bride.
See for yourself.
So you know nothing about him,
yet you followed him here?
I never thought he would even consider
getting married again.
Is it really true
that you and Uk are married?
That is why she is here.
She has a hard time believing
that you are married to Uk.
To be honest,
I find it hard to believe as well.
You must not have known about this.
Then you will understand why no one
believed that you were his bride.
See for yourself.
Young Master.
Did you just come home?
Yes, draw a bath for me.
What about Young Lady Bu-yeon?
Did you not see her?
She went to see you,
so I hurriedly packed
some honey biscuits for her.
You must have missed each other.
She seemed to be worried
because she could not find you.
She could be looking for you there.
I regained another memory,
and now I am able to do this.
Was it you who called me?
Yes, I heard they were a set.
I was the one who called for you.
But you did not come…
for me, did you?
Yes, I frantically rushed over here.
You better have
a good explanation for this.
What if I shared some good news
with you?
I regained another memory.
You and I…
have liked each other for a long time.
ALCHEMY OF SOULS
PART 2
People were massacred on a boat
crossing Lake Gyeongcheondaeho,
and they say it was Naksu's doing.
The soul shifter that appeared this time
is Naksu.
If you are so worried,
I will catch her myself.
How can he get rid of something
that does not exist?
That ridiculous rumor
could end up killing your daughter.
By any chance, are you not feeling well?
What is inside my body?
I would like to hold a banquet
outside the palace walls.
If Jin Bu-yeon gets attacked,
it will become Naksu's doing.
Then everything will become
Jang Uk's responsibility.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim